var quizListData = {
  "quizduration": 100,
  "quizName": "Force and Motion final Quiz",
  "quizId": "1",
  "questionslist": [
    {
      "questionType": "MULTI_CORRECT",
      "question": "Which of these are colors?",
      "correct_answer": ["Red", "Orange"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": ["Red", "Five", "Two", "Orange", "Ten"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "FILL_IN_THE_BLANKS",
      "question":
          "Things that are not moving, would not move without a ________ acting on them.",
      "correct_answer": ["force"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": []
    },
    {
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
      "question":
          "Place a ball on a flat surface (desk, table, or floor). What happens to the ball ?",
      "correct_answer": ["The ball moves"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": ["The ball does not move", "The ball moves"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "FILL_IN_THE_BLANKS",
      "question":
          "The more _______ an object has, the more force it takes  to move it.",
      "correct_answer": ["Mass"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": []
    },
    {
      "questionType": "FILL_IN_THE_BLANKS",
      "question": "For every action there is an equal and _______ reaction ",
      "correct_answer": ["opposite"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": []
    },
    {
      "questionType": "FILL_IN_THE_BLANKS",
      "question":
          "When you push the ball does not keep rolling forever,because ______ and friction slow it down.",
      "correct_answer": ["gravity"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": []
    },
    {
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
      "question":
          "Push the ball gently with your finger. What happens to the ball?",
      "correct_answer": ["The ball moves"],
      "marks": "4",
      "choices": ["The ball does not move", "The ball moves"]
    }
  ]
};
var multipleChoiceQuiz = {
  "quizduration": 100,
  "quizName": "Force and Motion final Quiz",
  "quizId": "1",
  "questionslist":[
    {
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "question":
    "Place a ball on a flat surface (desk, table, or floor). What happens to the ball ?",
    "correct_answer": ["The ball moves"],
    "marks": "2",
    "choices": ["The ball does not move", "The ball moves"],
    "success":"Great Job !"
  },{
    "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
    "question":
    "India's Capital ?",
    "correct_answer": ["Delhi"],
    "marks": "2",
    "choices": ["Delhi", "Mumbai","Hyderabd","Pune"],
      "success":"Nice Job !"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
      "question":
      "Is Java True Object Oriented Programing Language ?",
      "correct_answer": ["True"],
      "marks": "2",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "success":"Niceely Done !"
    }
  ],
};